

# Prima Jatnika

# Mobile Engineer

Hi everyone, my name is Prima Jatnika. I have experience as Software Developer especially as Fullstack Engineer and Mobile Engineer (iOS and Android) for more than 3 years in Banking application, MSME application and etc. with several projects such as Hasjrat, BNI, Bank Mestika. By using several languages including flutter, angular, kotlin, java and swift. Has experience as a mobile freelance using flutter for internal applications at EGP Security and KOPBI Indonesia. I'm used to using Git, postman, dbever to help with development needs.

## $\times$

primajatnika271995@gmail.c



+62 85875074351



40287, Bandung, Indonesia



linkedin.com/in/primajatnika



github.com/primajatnika27

# **SKILLS**

FLUTTER

DOCKER

JAVA

**SPRING BOOT** 

**ANGULAR** 

GO

**SWIFT** 

KOTLIN

**REST API** 

JETPACK COMPOSE

# LANGUAGES

#### Indonesian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### English

Professional Working Proficiency

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Mobile Engineer**

# PT.Majoo Indonesia

03/2022 - 02/2024

Malang, Indonesia

Banduna, Indonesia

Majoo is an integrated SaaS business solution platform that provides complete solutions for Indonesian MSMEs. Achievements/Tasks

- Work closely with Product and Engineering teams to understand requirements and translate them to elegant implementations for mobile platforms
- Build reusable mobile software components and develop mobile frameworks based on best practices

# **Fullstack Developer**

#### PT.Tabel Data Informatika

07/2018 - 03/2022

Company engaged in IT Consulting

Achievements/Tasks

- Kemenperin Industri Revolution 4.0 IOT Mobile App (IONIC)
- BNI Jaring Ummat Mobile App (Flutter)
- Hasjrat HCare Mobile App (Flutter)
- Hasjrat Sales Tools (Flutter)
- Bank Sumsel Babel (Kotlin)
- Bank Riau Kepri (Kotlin)
- BNI Agen46 (Java, Kotlin)
- Bank Mestika (Swift-UI)

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Palang Parkir Otomatis (08/2017 - 08/2017)

Develop Automatic Doorstop with Raspberry Microcontroller and display on Web App

ERPLAN (07/2023 - 08/2023)

- Create mobile app's like HRIS application
- https://github.com/primajatnika27/erplan

Clean Architecture Template Flutter (12/2023 - 12/2023)

https://github.com/primajatnika27/now-playing-flutter

## **INTERESTS**

MOBILE

IOT

WEB

**FULLSTACK** 

RnD

## **EDUCATION**

## **Study Programme**

**Indonesian Computer University** 

09/2013 - 03/2018

Courses

 Raspberry Pi based Portable fingerprint time attendance and Web App with Geolocation Security Bandung, Indonesia

ı